HUGO DAVIS

+34 691 854 931 ● HUGODAVIS1@GMAIL.COM C/ SANT DOMENEC DEL CALL 10, 08002, BARCELONA

ABOUT

Native Londoner currently studying in Barcelona for a Master in Digital Development. With five years of experience in banking, now keen to develop my career in the Digital Industry. Skilled in the use of HTML, CSS and JavaScript for front end web development, as well as Java for back end web and software development. I have a strong awareness of the concepts behind Agile, UX and Software Craftsmanship and I am also currently learning the Spanish language.

EDUCATION

2015 – 2016	Barcelona Technology School (Universitat de Barcelona)	
	Master in Digital Solutions Development	Currently studying for this master, which covers web and mobile development, cloud computing, big data, internet of things, UX, Agile, Software Craftsmanship, digital innovation & entrepreneurship
2005 – 2008	University of Leeds	
	BA (Hons) Economics	Three year degree course that provided quantitative, computing, analytical and presentation skills in a business context (Class: 2:1)
1998 – 2005	Forest School, London	
	A Level (2005)	Economics (A) Mathematics (B) Design and Technology (B)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Apr 2014 – July 2015 Macquarie Bank Limited, London Client Relationship Management

- Front office investment bank role. Client onboarding.
- Managed the Onboarding, Credit, Legal and Compliance teams to ensure bank clients were cleared to the required regulatory standard.
- Strong relationships with the various trading desks on the Commodities and Financial Markets trading floor and in-depth knowledge of the products being traded and how they were traded.
- High level relationship building, problem solving, time management and communication skills demonstrated consistently.

Feb 2011 – Apr 2014 Macquarie Bank Limited, London Trade Floor Support Analyst

- IT support for Macquarie Bank's Commodities and Financial Markets trading floor.
- Sitting front office, responsible for hardware and application support.
- In-depth technical knowledge of bespoke trading applications was required, including Trayport, PATS, Bloomberg and Fidessa.
- Time management and the ability to prioritise incoming issues. Technical problem solving.
- Exposure to UNIX, SQL and Python. Experience in networking, storage and virtualization.

Dec 2009 – Feb 2011 Algrove Limited, London

Research Analyst

• Research analysis and administrative support for this buy to let property development company. Organized the acquisition, development and letting of properties.

Nov 2009 – Nov 2010 Gala Coral Group, London

Manager

- Bookmaking retail environment. Ran the Crouch End Coral branch.
- Promoted to shop manager.

Summer 2007

Price waterhouse Coopers (PwC), Dublin

Intern

• Internship in the Financial Services department within the Tax and Legal Services practice. Preparing tax returns and assisting in providing tax advice for various clients.

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS AND SKILLS

IT Qualifications/Courses Completed:

- ITIL Foundation Certificate in IT Service Management
- A+ Essentials with Windows 7
- Planning and Managing Windows 7 Desktop Deployments and Environments

Financial Regulatory Qualifications:

• Chartered Institute for Securities & Investment – UK Financial Regulation

Additional IT Skills:

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, Android, iOS, Python.
- Advanced competency with: Microsoft Word, Access, Excel and PowerPoint.
- GCSE grade A* in Information Technology.
- Adobe Photoshop and Dreamweaver for website production.